

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991

E-mail: hello@naushikha.com

Website: naushikha.com

COMPUTER ENTHUSIAST

PROFILE

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with nearly 3 years of cumulative industrial working experience in fields such as game testing, networking, customer support and tutoring.

Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

PLAYTESTER

Arimac (Jan 2021 - May 2021)

• Testing and evaluating Android mobile games

VIRTUAL INTERN

Nestlé (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

• Researching for the supply-chain division to localize use of raw materials

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration
- Server and desktop hardware configuration

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Voigue (Dec 2017 - Jan 2018)

 Support team services to handle Daraz.lk's excess user traffic during Christmas

INTERN

Third Space Global (Dec 2016 - Jan 2017)

• Online tutoring mathematics for school children stationed in the UK

SKILLS

- Linux, networking and system administration
- WebGL graphics and web design
- Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Fluent communication

EDUCATION

BSC (HONS) COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

• Current GPA: 3.8 (out of 4.0)

0/L, A/L

Ananda College, Colombo 10. (2003 - 2016)

• Ordinary Level : 9 As

• Advanced Level: Z-Score - 2.3634, Island Rank - 8, District Rank - 2







DOMAIN RELATED INFO

Stated below are a list of projects I have done on my own or developed with the help of a team. These are selected primarily on the basis that they are very closely related to the domain of graphics, game development or simulation.

PROJECTS

WHEN ONCE THE SKY WAS BLUE

Immersive 360° Web Experience - 2021

- Designed using Three.js, pure HTML, CSS and JS.
- Built to showcase at the Women's Theatre Festival '21- "WTFRINGE21".
- Completed entire experience within a short span of 2 weeks. <u>Trailer Link</u> | Request for Demo

SATURNX

A Three.js Demonstration - 2021

- Designed using Three.js, pure HTML, CSS and JS.
- Demo Link

VACCINE HUNT

2D Side Scrolling Platformer - 2021

- Made with a team for the Global Game Jam 2021 using Unity.
- Was in charge of lighting, sound design and some bug fixing.
 Download Link

HARD DUOS

1vs1 Multiplayer Attacker-Defender Game - 2019

- Made with a team for the IEEE GameRush Hackathon 2019 using Unreal.
- 2nd runner up in the competition.
- Was overseeing sound design and presentation.
 Presentation Link

TEST ARENA

3D First Person Shooter - 2017

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Personal project to explore boundaries of VB6 + TV3D.
 Write-up Link | Demo Video

COMMAND ATTACK 3

3D First Person Shooter - 2012

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Built to showcase at the "Anada Abhiman" exhibition of Ananda College.
- Completed 2 levels for the game in 2 weeks, including story, cutscenes and gameplay mechanics.
 Write-up Link

SOCIETIES

SEDS UOC

Web Development Manager - 2021

- Leading the creation and maintenance of <u>SEDS UOC website</u> and <u>blog</u>.
- Handling all the web-related technicalities of the organization.

ICT SOCIETY

Member

- Ananda College
- Created 'Command Attack 3' and an interactive presentation.

ENGLISH DEBATING SOCIETY

Member

- Ananda College
- Have participated in numerous debating competitions.







ADDITIONAL INFO

Stated below are a list of projects, certifications and competitions that are outside to the domain that is being applied for.

PROJECTS

SLMOSYS

Content and Exam Management System - 2021

- Designed using pure PHP, HTML, CSS and JS.
- Built for the Sri Lanka Olympiad Mathematics Foundation along with a development team.

Demo Link

SPOTIFY WIDGET

Cloudflare Powered Middleware - 2021

- Runs as a serverless application on Cloudflare.
- Open source solution that can embed your currently playing song on Spotify in a website as a widget.
 Article Link

LIGHTER FRAMEWORK

PHP MVC Framework - 2021

- Based on the initial SLMOsys framework I designed.
- Modular and a somewhat opinionated framework but is a great lightweight framework to kickstart small PHP MVC applications. <u>Repo Link</u>

SORTIE

The Moodle Sorter! - 2021

- Designed using React.
- Helps to easily extract and sort assignments and announcements from any Moodle.
- Used internally at the university by me and friends.
 <u>App Link</u>

ECOEARTH.LK

Web Design - 2020

- Designed using WordPress.
- Minimalistic web development that runs on free services Cloudflare, ForwardEmail and InfinityFree.
 Website Link

PERECTITLANKA.COM

Web Design - 2021

- Designed using WordPress.
- Ongoing project that is still under development.
 Website Link

SEDSUOC.LK

Web and Blog Design - 2021

- Designed using pure HTML, CSS, JS and WordPress.
- As the web development manager of SEDS UOC, I am currently leading the team to create and maintain the website and blog.
 Website Link | Blog Link







CERTIFICATIONS

GOOGLE CLOUD

SRE and DevOps Engineer with Google Cloud Specialization (Mar 2021)

Getting Started with Google Kubernetes Engine (Mar 2021)

Logging, Monitoring and Observability in Google Cloud (Mar 2021)

Reliable Google Cloud Infrastructure: Design and Process (Mar 2021)

Developing a Google SRE Culture (Feb 2021)

Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure (Dec 2020)

[|S[]] Networking Essentials (Jan 2021)

Introduction to Cybersecurity (Dec 2020)

NDG Linux Unhatched (Dec 2020)

SOPHOS Sophos Certified Engineer (Nov 2018)

ET15 - Sophos Central Endpoint and Server v1.0 - Engineer (Nov 2018)

ET80 - XG Firewall v17.0 - Engineer (Nov 2018)

ET01 - Sophos Central Overview - Engineer (Nov 2018)

SOLOLEARN

Java Tutorial Course (Oct 2018)

PHP Tutorial Course (Oct 2018)

C++ Tutorial Course (Aug 2018)

JavaScript Tutorial Course (Oct 2017)

HTML Fundamentals Course (Mar 2017)

SQL Fundamentals Course (Apr 2017)

Diploma in Office Application (Jan 2011)

COMPETITIONS

ISACA

iCS - Hack the World - 2021

- Inter university capture the flag (CTF) cybersecurity competition.
- Our team got short-listed from the initial knockout round.

SLIIT

NetCom Competition-2021

Inter university networking competition.

SLUD

Global Game Jam - 2021

- 48-hour long annual distributed game jam where we create a game.
- Our team participated representing Sri Lanka Unity Developers and built 'Vaccine Hunt' for this competition.

IFFF

IEEE Xtreme 14.0 - 2021

• 24-hour long hackathon to solve competitive programming problems.

IEEE GameRush - 2021

- 24-hour long hackathon to design a computer game.
- Our team secured the third place in the competition, with the game 'Hard Duos'.







REFERENCES

AIR CDRE (RETD) JAYASIRI AMARASENA CEO

DR. MANJUSRI WICKRAMASINGHE **Senior Lecturer**

B.Sc Hons in CS (col), PhD (Monash) University of Colombo School of Computing

mie@ucsc.cmb.ac.lk | 071 316 8483

HIMARUK SILVA **Software Engineer**

SimCentric Technologies <u>himaruks@simct.com</u> | <u>077 540 1352</u>





